<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Android15Snippet-post35</string>

    <string name="button_next">Next</string>

    <!-- behavior changes -->
    <string name="bc_page_size_actual">Device page size is: %1$s bytes</string>
    <string name="bc_page_size_big">Devices with Android 15 or higher might have 16KB page size</string>
    <string name="bc_page_size_small">Devices with Android 14 or lower have 4KB page size</string>
    <string name="bc_screen_recording_hidden">You should see the recording indicator while the recording is active.\n On the recording, the notification should not be displayed.</string>
    <string name="bc_screen_recording_hint">Start sharing the screen (via Screen Recorder, Zoom etc) and send the notification.\n Check the recording afterwards</string>
    <string name="bc_screen_recording_visible">You probably have no special recording indicator. \n On the recording, you should see the notification content.</string>
    <string name="bc_send_notification">Send simple notification</string>
    <string name="bc_toggle_dnd">Toggle Do-Not-Disturb Mode</string>
    <string name="bc_toggle_dnd_hint">You should only be able to turn off Do-Not-disturb mode if it was not set manually or by other apps. This is due to the AutomaticZenRules that are responsible for that now.</string>

    <!-- developer tools -->
    <string name="dev_tools_flex_string">Flex font family became better is some ways but even more insufferable in others</string>

    <!-- notifications -->
    <string name="notification_channel_name">Notification Channel</string>
    <string name="notification_channel_description">Channel description</string>
    <string name="notification_title">My Notification</string>
    <string name="notification_text">Notification text</string>
    <string name="notification_title_scheduled">Scheduled Notification</string>
    <string name="notification_text_scheduled">Scheduled notification text</string>

    <!-- private space -->
    <string name="private_space_create_file_button">Create Text File</string>
    <string name="private_space_hint">Install the app to private space to test these changes</string>
    <string name="private_space_install_hint">This is not the same app instance as in the public space. This is a separate, second installation of the app</string>
    <string name="private_space_notification_visibility_hint">Press the button below to start receiving repeating notifications. They should work even if you close the app. You might have to go to settings and allow an app to schedule alarms if the app doesn\'t request it by itself.\n After you close private space, all app\'s notifications should be automatically deleted and new notifications should stop.</string>
    <string name="private_space_picked_file_content">Picked File Content: %1$s</string>
    <string name="private_space_pick_file_hint">The only way to see public files for private space apps is using file picker. Obviously it doesn\'t work in the other direction.</string>
    <string name="private_space_pick_file_button">Pick and Read File</string>
    <string name="private_space_read_file_button">Read File</string>
    <string name="private_space_start_repeating_notifications">Start Repeating Notifications</string>
    <string name="private_space_stop_repeating_notifications">Stop Repeating Notifications</string>
    <string name="private_space_storage_hint">Storage is separated between private and public space. Press the first button to create a file, and second one to read it. You should only be able to read files created by the public version of the app by the public version of the app, same goes for private version</string>
    <string name="private_space_visibility_hint">After you close the private space, information about this app being opened will be cleared from the recents menu. Information about them is not even available in the settings menu. There is no way to even know if this app is installed without opening the private space.</string>

    <!-- screen labels -->
    <string name="label_behavior_changes">Behavior Changes</string>
    <string name="label_developer_tools">Developer Tools</string>
    <string name="label_private_space">Private Space</string>

</resources>